I. Feinberg, Robert Arbitration Records 5548
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- [F342] Soloff & Wechsler, Inc. 1/24/73, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 48)
- [F343] Sommer-Burgner, Inc., 1970 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  Decisions: 1) 7/29/70. Vacation pay. 2) 11/18/70. Back pay award; holiday pay; vacation pay. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [F344] Sonnenblick-Braunschweig, Inc. 7/7/72, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 50)
  Decision: Elimination of jobs. Contains notes.
- [F345] Spear & Picardi., 1969-1973 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  Decisions: 1) 1/28/69. Overtime. 2) 9/24/69. Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages. Contains notes and correspondence. 3) 10/14/71. Sick leave. Contains notes. 4) 6/20/73. Discharge; training & trial periods. Contains notes.
- [F346] Spokane Furs, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 52)
  Decisions: 1) 9/19/69. Strikes, slowdowns & work stoppages. 2) 9/24/69. Interpretation of past arbitration award. Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages; damages. Contains notes and correspondence. 3) 4/29/70. Contracting out.
- [F347] Leonard Springer, Inc., 1968 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  Decisions: 1) 10/23/68. Overtime. 2) 10/23/68. Rates of pay; repayment to employer. Contains notes.
- [F348] Stark & Alchas, Inc. 2/6/75., 1975 (Box 39, Folder 54)
- [F349] Walt Stiel, Inc. 2/6/75, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 55)
  Decision: Holiday pay; Vacation pay.
- [F350] Stogel Hanover, Spruch, Inc. 12/31/69, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 56)
  Decision: Merger; crew size. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F351] Stogel & Stark, Inc. 11/4/70, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 57)
  Decision: Successor company; crew size. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F352] Stogel & Weisberger, Inc. 3/1/71, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 58)
  Decision: Successor company; recall.
- [F353] Strassburg & Tama, Inc. 1/23/74, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 59)
- [F354] Sunbrook Furs, Inc., 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 60)
  Decisions: 1) 2/5/71. Successor company; crew size; rates of pay; fringe benefits. Contains notes. 2) 1/24/73. Vacation pay. 3) 1/24/73. Vacation pay.
- [F355] Sussman & Gettman. 1/2/73, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 61)
- [F356] Sutton Furs. 2/23/73, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 62)
  Decision: Vacation pay; successor company. Contains notes.
- [F357] Taubman & Greenspan, Inc. 11/20/68, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 63)
  Decision: Contractual duties; hiring. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F358] Taubman & Osofsky, Inc. 2/20/74, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 64)
- [F359] Joseph Teich., 1968 (Box 39, Folder 65)
  Decision: 1) 10/4/68. Overtime. 2) 11/27/68. Back pay award; holiday pay; vacation pay.
- [F360] Thomas & Kaiser, Inc. 3/17/71, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 66)
  Decision: Vacation pay. Contains correspondence
- [F361] Tikalsky & Glassman., 1969-1971 (Box 39, Folder 67)
  Decision: 1) 7/29/69. Contracting out. 2) 2/24/71. Vacation pay.
- [F362] Tobak & Nogler Furs, Inc. 5/15/74., 1974 (Box 39, Folder 68)
  Decision: Overtime. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F363] Trademark Fur Corp. 6/21/72, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 69)
  Decision: Back pay award; vacation pay.
- [F364] Morris Tucker & Co., Inc. 9/16/70, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 70)
- [F365] Turan Fur. 10/21/69, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 71)
  Decision: Back pay award; holiday; vacation pay. Contains correspondence.
- [F366] Turk-Tucker Furs, Inc., 1968-1972 (Box 39, Folder 72)
  Decisions: 1) 8/30/68. Employer-union relations; damages. Contains notes and correspondence. 2) 3/29/72. Vacation pay.
- [F367] Morris Turner, 1968-1974 (Box 39, Folder 73)
  Decisions: 1) 11/27/68. Sick leave & sick pay. Contains notes. 2) 9/4/74. Back pay award; holiday pay.
- [F368] Valencia Furs, Inc., 1972 (Box 39, Folder 74)
  Decisions: 1) 1/14/72. Repayment to employer; vacation pay. Contains notes. 2) 3/22/72. Contracting out.
- [F369] Valerie Fur Corp., 1971-1975 (Box 39, Folder 75)
  Decisions: 1) 2/3/71. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 2) 3/29/72. Holiday pay. 3) 3/24/75. Reduction in force. Contains correspondence.
- [F370] Varsity Furs. 3/24/71, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 76)
- [F371] Thomas Vassel Furs. 3/26/73, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 77)
- [F372] Venus Fur Wholesalers, Inc., 1969 (Box 39, Folder 78)
  Decisions: 1) 7/28/69. Overtime. Contains notes. 2) 7/28/69. Removal of work from the bargaining unit. Contains notes. 3) 7/28/69. Contractual duties; schedules of work. Contains notes.
- [F373] Venus Furs - Zwerdling - Gold, Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 39, Folder 79)
  Decisions: 1) 3/5/70. Reductions in force. Contains notes and correspondence. 2) 4/1/70. Overtime; removal of work from the bargaining unit; supervisors & foremen. Contains notes. 3) 4/9/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay; quits. Contains notes. 4) 2/3/71.
- [F374] Leo Vogel Furs. 12/17/73., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 80)
  Decision: Vacation pay (computation); termination of business.
- [F375] Wagner Fur Sales, Inc. 3/14/74, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 81)
  Decision: Discharge; insubordination; improper personal conduct. Contains notes.
- [F376] Morris Wagner & Sons, Inc., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 82)
  Decisions: 1) 6/14/73. Discharge; absences. Contains notes. 2) 10/4/73. Identification of employer. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [F377] Wasserman & Lavine, Inc., 1968-1973 (Box 39, Folder 83)
  Decisions: 1) 4/19/68. Assignment of jobs; equalization. 2) 4/26/68. Vacation pay. Contains notes. 3) 2/1/73. Reduction in force. Contains correspondence. 4) 6/14/73. Holiday pay.
- [F378] Waverly Furs. 1/27/71, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 84)
- [F379] Joseph Weiner Furs, Inc. 5/21/68, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 85)
  Decision: Falsification; files. Contains notes.
- [F380] Furs and Martin Weiner., 1970-1972 (Box 39, Folder 86)
  Decisions: 1) 3/4/70. Vacation pay. 2) 9/21/72. Welfare funds; vacation pay. Contains notes.
- [F381] Weinig Fur Trading Corp., 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 87)
  Decisions: 1) 1/30/74. Vacation pay. Contains notes and exhibits. 2) 2/20/74. Back pay award. Contains notes. 3) 5/8/74. Welfare funds; vacation pay. 4) 6/26/74. Vacation pay. Contains notes. 5) 12/26/74. Vacation pay. Contains notes. 6) 6/25/75. As in 5.
- [F382A] J. Weinig & Son, 1968-1971 (Box 39, Folder 88)
  Decisions: 1) 1/19/68. Sick leave and sick pay. Contains notes and correspondence. 2) 1/23/69. Union security. 3) 11/3/69. Removal of work from the bargaining unit. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits. 4) 1/3/69. Bonuses; overtime. 5) 11/3/69. Int
- [F382B] F. Weinig & Son., 1971-1974 (Box 39, Folder 89)
  Decisions: 1) 6/30/71. Sick leave and sick pay. 2) 9/20/72. Vacation pay. Contains notes. 3) 10/20/72. As in 2. 4) 6/20/73. Welfare funds. 5) 7/3/73. Vacation pay. 6) 2/20/74. Back pay award. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [F383] Weinstein & Geronimo, Inc., 1970 (Box 39, Folder 90)
  Decisions: 1) 1/28/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 2) 11/18/70. Holiday pay. 3) 12/31/70. Falsification; call-in. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [F384] Weintraub & Rothblat, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 91)
  Decision: 1) 6/28/68. Union security. Contains notes. 2) 9/26/68. Overtime.
- [F385] Sol Weissman, Inc., 1968-1971 (Box 39, Folder 92)
  Decisions: 1) 10/23/68. Falsification. Files; overtime. 2) 10/20/71. Overtime.
- [F386] Weitzman Bros., Inc., 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 93)
  Decision: 1) 12/10/71. Vacation pay. 2) 3/6/73. Vacation pay; termination of business. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F387] Wilshire Trading Corp. 1/21/70, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 94)
  Decision: files; holiday pay; vacation pay.
- [F388] Philip Winisk Fur Corp., 1970-1974 (Box 39, Folder 95)
  Decisions: 1) 3/12/70. Discharge; insubordination; quits. Contains notes and exhibits. 2) 7/20/72. Vacation pay; quits. Contains notes and exhibits. 3) 2/6/74. Holiday pay; vacation pay.
- [F389] Ben Wirtzbaum Furs, Inc., 1968-1972 (Box 39, Folder 96)
  Decision: 1) 5/2/68. Removal of work from the bargaining unit. 2) 11/2/72 Contracting out.
- [F390] David Wolf Furs, Inc. 10/15/69, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 97)
  Decision: Discharge; removal of work from the bargaining unit. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F391] Wolfe-Miller Corp. 5/2/68, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 98)
- [F392] Woliver Bros. 1/2/74, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 99)
- [F393] Wollman Furs. 9/2/70, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 100)
  Decision: vacation pay. Contains correspondence.
- [F394] Woloch Furs. 1/27/71, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 101)
- [F395] Woloch, Prince & Ware, Inc. 6/27/75, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 102)
  Decision: discharge; insubordination; improper personal conduct. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F396] Zacher Furs, Inc. 9/8/71, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 103)
- [F397] Zeiger & Green, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 104)
  Decisions: 1) 5/2/68. Overtime. 2) 1/22/69. Successor company; crew size. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F398] Bernard Zenn, Inc. 9/8/71, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 105)
- [F399] Zingman & Niedelman, Inc. 4/29/70, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 106)
- [F400] Zodiac Fur Mfg. Co., Inc. 2/20/74, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 107)
- [F401] Homer Zograph, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 108)
  Decisions: 1) 1/23/69. Overtime. 2) 2/11/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 3) 5/20/70. Vacation pay.
- [*518] The Paper Assn. of N.Y.C. and Paper Workers and Distributing Trades Union, Local 1447. Settled 6/26/46, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  Issue: rates of pay.
- [*1000] Towns & James, Inc. and Federal Local Union #20734. Settled 1/20/74., 1974 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- [*1002A-E] Miscellaneous Arbitration Cases Settled, Withdrawn, or Adjourned, and other arbitration materials. (Box 40, Folder 3)
- [*1005] Specialty Bakery Owners of America and Retail Bakery and Confectionary Employees Union, Local 1111. Settled 4/23/74., 1974 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- [*1006] A. DePinna Co. and DSWEU, Local 1499., 1947 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  Withdrawn 2/27/47. Issue: rates of pay.
- [*1050] A. Finkenberg's Son and Retail, Furniture & Floor Covering Employees Union, Local 853, CIO., 1948 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  Settled 8/16/48. Issues: rates of pay, schedules of work.
- [*1080] United Looseleaf Corp. and Pocketbook Worker Union of N.Y. and UMW, Local 178, United Construction Workers. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  NLRB case, withdrawn. Issues: Inter-union disputes, violence, strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages.
- [*1088] The Hills Bros. Co. and Food, Tobacco, Agricultural & Allied Workers of America, Local 207, CIO., 1948 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  Adjourned 4/26/48. Issue: Contract negotiation.
- [*1127] Volco Brass & Copper Co. and Int'l Union of Mine, Mill & Smelter Workers, Local 673., 1949 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  Did not accept I.R. Feinberg as arbitrator. 1/6/49. Issues: Layoffs, incentive pay and incentive systems.
- [*1128] Conmar Products Corp. and UE, Local 424., 1948 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  Settled 11/23/48. Issue: Incentive pay and incentive systems.
- [*1140] Revlon Products Corp. and Wholesale & Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65, CIO., 1949 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  Settled 4/28/49. Issue: Rates of pay, cost of living increases.
- [*1148] Hinnekens Machine Co., Inc. and IAM, Dist. 161, Peterson Lodge #1703., 1949 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  Settled 6/2/49. Issues: Layoffs, seniority.
- [*1149] Interborough News Co., and Auto Mechanics and Helpers, Gasoline Station & Parking Attendants Union, Local 917., 1949 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  Settled 6/22/49. Issues: Layoffs; seniority.
- [*1151] American Package Co. and Paper Box Makers Union, Local 299., 1949 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  Settled 7/7/49. Issues: Back pay award, rates of pay.
- [*1156] File of Background Information on the Newspaper & Mail Deliverers' Union (NMD) of N.Y. (Box 40, Folder 15)
  Includes union newspaper, collective agreements and other material.
- [*1166] Manhattan News Co., Inc. and N.M.D., 1949 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  Includes hearings as impartial chairman between the parties. 12/1/49 and 12/14/49. Issues: Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages.
- [*1176A] Daily Mirror and NMD., 1950 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  Adjourned 3/8/50. Issue: Contracting out, removal of work from the bargaining unit.
- [*1176B] Daily Mirror and NMD., 1950 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  Postponed 5/18/50. Issue: Contracting out, removal of work from the bargaining unit.
- [*1261] Otis Elevator Co. and UAW, CIO., 1951 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  Adjourned 5/17/51. Issue: Promotion.
- [*1279] Parade Publications, Inc. and Newspaper Guild of N.Y., Local 3., 1952 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  Withdrawn 5/1/52. Issue: Leaves of absence.
- [*1290] Friedland Fixtures and Local 150., 1952 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  Adjourned as of 9/5/52. Issues: Vacation pay, discharge, removal of work from the bargaining unit, supervisors and foremen.
- [*1306] Revlon Products, Inc. and DPOWA, Dist. 65., 1952 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  Settled 7/30/52. Issue: Reinstatement.
- [*1311] Tex-Ray Fabrics, Inc. and TWUA, CIO, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  Withdrawn 9/9/57. Issues: Holiday pay, incentive pay and incentive systems.
- [*1319] N.Y. Times Co. and Newspaper Guild of N.Y., Local 3 ANG, CIO., 1953 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  Settled 1/27/53. Issue: Reinstatement.
- [*1332] Rodic Chemical & Rubber Corp. and URW, Local 372., 1953 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  Settled 6/8/53. Issue: Layoffs, seniority.
- [*1330] Hearst Metrotone News, Inc. and IATSE, Local 771., 1953 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  Settled 6/15/53. Issue: Discharge, severance pay.
- [*1380] E.R. Squibb & Sons, Div. of Olin-Mathieson Chemical Corp., 1955 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  Withdrawn 5/9/55. Issue: promotion.
- [*1396] Arma Corp. and Engineers Assn. of Arma., 1955 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  Adjourned 6/2/55. Issue: Working conditions.
- [*1406] Plume & Atwood Mfg. Co. and UAW, Local 1251, CIO., 1955 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  Withdrawn 10/21/55.
- [*1407] NBC, Inc. and AFTRA, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  Postponed 4/16/56. Issue: Back pay award.
- [*1408] Natvar Corp. and Int'l Paperworkers of America, CIO., 1955 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  Settled 8/15/55
- [*1419] Int'l News Service and the Commercial Telegraphers Union AFL., 1955 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  Withdrawn 12/12/55.
- [*1426] Allied N.Y. Services, Inc. and Coal, Gasoline and Fuel Oil Teamsters Union, Local 553., 1955 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  Feinberg withdraws from case 10/18/55. Decision: discharge.
- [*1436] Union Engineering Corp. and IUMSW, Local 15., 1956 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  Settled 2/2/56. Decision: Rates of pay.
- [*1439] CBS, Inc. and IBEW, Radio & TV Broadcast Engineers Union, Local 1212., 1956 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  Settled 2/24/56. Issues: Notice, assignment of jobs.
- [*1451A&B] Jack L. Honig Inc. and ILGWU, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  IRF is the Co. attorney in a wage reopening case, settled 10/3/57.
- [*1463] Julia Feather Novelties, 1956-1957 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  Materials in Role as Attorney and consultant.
- [*1492] Clarke Bros. Mfg. Co., Inc. (Box 40, Folder 38)
  Labor Relations Council material including those concerning negotiations leading to consent election proceedings before the NLRB.
- [*1519] Holdeman vs. International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots, Inc., 1959 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  This file encompasses all the materials surrounding the 1959 election of union officers. Included is an arbitration award allowing Mr. Feinberg the scope to oversee the elections, and a large volume of material re nominating procedures, the ballots, and t
- [*1534] Rubin Bros. and IBT, Local 807., 1959 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  Settled 9/16/59. Issue: Contract negotiations.
- [*1569] New Jersey Aluminum Extrusion Co. and USA, Local 5136, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  Withdrawn 12/12/60
- [*1571] Monroe Calculating Machine Co., Div. of Litton Industries and IUE, Local 432, AFL-CIO., 1961 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  Postponed 1/17/61
- [*1575] Lockheed Aircraft Service - N.Y., Inc. and IAM, Lodge 1834., 1961 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  Settled 2/2/61
- [*1578] New Jersey Aluminum Extrusion Co. and USA, Local 5136, AFL-CIO, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  Withdrawn 8/29/61
- [*1579] The Trane Co. and PPF, Local 730., 1961 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  Settled 3/22/61. Issue: Discharge; insubordination; improper personal conduct.
- [*1586] Walrath Beach & Storrowton Music Fair and AAA-AEA., 1961 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  Settled 10/8/61. Issue: Back pay award.
- [*1592] Publishers Bureau of New Jersey and New Jersey Newspaper Guild, American Newspaper Guild., 1961 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  Feinberg resigns 10/5/61. Issue: Compensation, inability to work (lockout).
- [*1595] The Okonite Co. and IBEW, Local 1992, AFL-CIO, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  Settled 8/24/61. Issue: Layoff
- [*1596] Montrose Motor Sales Corp. and UAW, Local 259., 1961 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  Settled 1/9/61. Issues: Discharge, absences.
- [*1618] Hotel Hershey and BCW, Local 464., 1962 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  Settled 9/14/62. Issue: rates of pay.
- [*1637A-C] New York Naval Shipyards and Pattern makers Assn. of N.Y. and Vicinity, and American Fed. Of Tech. Engineers., 1963 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  This file contains material accumulated by Mr. Feinberg in his role as arbitrator in the N.Y. Naval Shipyard in Brooklyn, N.Y. He was appointed under Executive Order 10988 as the workers at the shipyards are federal employees. The issue in question concer
- [*1644A] Phelps Dodge Refining Corp. and USA, Local 4355 AFL-CIO, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  Withdrawn 5/29/64
- [*1644B] Phelps Dodge Refining Corp. and USA, Local 4355, AFL-CIO, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  Withdrawn 3/6/64
- [*1647] Arma Div. of American Bosch Arma Corp. and Engineers Assn. of Arma, Local 418 (UE), AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  Settled 12/12/63. Issue: layoffs
- [*1650] Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., Inc. (Frederick W. Schmidt, Inc.) And N.Y. Typographical Union #6., 1963 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  Adjourned 11/18/63.
- [*1653] American Bosch Arma Corp., Arma Div. and IUE, Local 418, AFL-CIO., 1964 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  Settled 6/10/64. Issue: Bumping.
- [*1657] El Al Israel Airlines and IAM, Lodge #1894, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  Withdrawn 1/23/64. Issue: improper work practices.
- [*1680] Westinghouse Electric Corp. and IUE, Local #617, AFL-CIO, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  Withdrawn 10/22/64. Issue: Back pay award.
- [*1682] American Car & Foundry Div. ACF Industries, Inc. and USA, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  Settled 11/12/64. Issue: Discharge.
- [*1688] The Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co., Newark Bakery, Queen Street Plant and BCW, Local 262, AFL-CIO., 1965 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  Withdrawn 1/13/65
- [*1689] Allied Building Metal Industries and BSIW, Local 455, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  Settled 1/15/65. Issue: Recall.
- [*1694] Alco Gravure Div. of Publication Corp. and N.Y. Printing Pressmen's Union, Local 2, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  Adjourned 9/7/66. Issue: Grievances and grievance procedures.
- [*1702] Board of Education, N.Y.C. and UFT, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  Settled 11/30/65
- [*1704] Ford Instrument Co. and IUE, Local 471., 1965 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  Settled 7/12/65. Issue: layoff.
- [*1705] Moving & Warehousemen Assn. of Greater N.Y. and IBT, Local 814., 1965 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  Withdrawn 6/7/65. Issue: Strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages.
- [*1708] Lamson Corp. and Federal Labor Union #21664., 1965 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  Settled 11/17/65. Issue: Classification of jobs, evaluation of job factors, rates of pay.
- [*1709A] Joseph Kipness (individually and as producer of the musical "La Grosse Valise" and AAA-AEA, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  Settled 4/8/66. Issue: Back pay award.
- [*1709B] David Merrick (Ginger Rogers - "Hello Dolly") and AAA-AEA., 1967 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  Settled 7/6/67. Issue: Contractual duties.
- [*1712] Printers League Section (Joseph Berg Mfg. Co., Inc.) and N.Y. Typographical Union #6., 1966 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  Settled 6/2/66. Issue: Contracting out.
- [*1729] Republic Aviation Division, Fairchild Hiller and IAM, Republic Lodge 1987, AFL-CIO., 1967 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  Settled 7/18/67. Issue: Classification of jobs, rates of pay.
- [*1750A] Personal Products Corp. and United Papermakers and Paper Workers, Local 535., 1967 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  Withdrawn 6/9/67
- [1750B] Personal Products Corp. and United Papermakers and Paper Workers, Local 535., 1967 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  Withdrawn 12/15/67.
- [*1752] Caterpillar Tractor Co. and IAM, Local #851., 1967 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  Settled 6/15/67
- [*1755] Gifford Oil, Inc. and IBT, Local 553., 1967 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  Settled 7/7/67. Issue: Discharge.
- [*1759] General Dynamics Corp. and IAM, Local 1871., 1967 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  Settled 9/7/67. Issue: Medical release.
- [*1761A-D] Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority and Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Employees, AFSCME, Local 1396., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  Fact finding report and recommendations, issued 1/9/68. In this case, Mr. Feinberg was a member of a three man fact-finding board under the Taylor Law. Of interest is that this was the first fact-finding panel set up under the new statute. The issue invol
- [*1763] Humble Oil & Refinery Co. and IBT, Local 866., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  Settled 2/29/68. Issue: Overtime; premium pay.
- [*1767] Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. and OCAW, Local 8-2340., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  Adjourned 1/22/68.
- [*1769] Ormont Machine Co., Inc. and IBT, Local 810., 1969 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  Settled 4/25/69. Issue: Classification of jobs.
- [*1779A-C] City of N.Y. and the Judicial Conference of the State of N.Y. and CWA, Local 1180, AFL-CIO., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  Report and recommendations of the impasse panel dated 6/18/68. This case is another first as it was the first in which an impasse panel was set up by the NYC Office of Collective Bargaining. The impasse was in the area of contract negotiations.
- [*1785] NBC and IATSE, Film Editors, Local 771., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  Settled 11/13/68. Issue: Union security.
- [*1786] Carrier Corp. and SMW, Local 527., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  Settled 12/4/68. Issues: Assignment of jobs; working conditions; safety.
- [*1790] Allied Building Metal Industries. (for Albro Metal Products Corp.) and Shopmen's Local Union 455, AFL-CIO., 1969 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  Settled 6/30/69. Issue: Rates of pay.
- [*1791] Seaboard World Airlines and ALPA., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  Adjourned 9/27/68.
- [*1794A&B] City of N.Y. and District No. 1, Pacific Coast District, Marine Engineers Beneficial Assn., AFL-CIO. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  This is another impasse panel case set up by the Office of Collective Bargaining of NYC to deal with a breakdown in contract negotiations between the City and the personnel who operate NYC's fire boats.
- [*1797] Hewitt Robins, Inc., Whitney Chain Div. and UAW, Local 1199., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  Settled 11/19/68. Issue: Discharge.
- [*1802] Pratt & Whitney, Inc. and Unity Lodge, Local 405., 1969 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  Settled 6/12/69. Issue: Classification of jobs; premium pay.
- [*1815] Humble Oil & Refining Co. and IBT, Local 866., 1970 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  Settled 1/29/70.
- [*1817] Allied N.Y. Services, Inc. and IBT, Local 553., 1970 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  Withdraw 7/7/70. Issue: Discharge
- [*1822] Printers League Section, Printing Industries of Metropolitan N.Y., 1970 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  Settled 7/24/70. Issue; Discharge; alcoholism, drinking and intoxication; fights and altercations.
- [*1837] City of N.Y. and Deputy Sheriff's Assn. Findings of fact and conclusions., 1971 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  4/27/71. This is another three-man impasse panel hearing under the Office of Collective Bargaining of N.Y. The issue is contract negotiations in the areas of salary schedules, bonuses, welfare funds and pension plans. Included are the findings of facts, n
- [*1844] United Aircraft and Industrial Aircraft Lodge #1746., 1971 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  Settled 8/18/71 and 8/23/71.
- [*1852] General Dynamics Corp. and IAM, Local Lodge 1871., 1952 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  Settled 4/7/52. Issue: Assignment to work outside classification.
- [*1858] Celanese Plastics Co. and TWUA, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  Withdrawn 4/28/72. Issue: Discharge.
- [*1975A&B] Miscellaneous correspondence related to arbitration matters, 1969-1975 (Box 43, Folder 1)